Preliminary Guide to the Africa News Service (Durham, N.C.) Leroy T. Walker Africa News Service Archive, 1952-1998 and undated (bulk 1952-1994)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Africa: Countries (Box 24)
  - Zimbabwe (Box 192)
    - Military (Box 204)
      - 1983-1994, (2 folders) (Box 204)
      - Arms Supplies, 1977-1993 (Box 204)
      - Liberation Forces, 1975-1986 (Box 204)
      - Massacres, 1973-1984 (Box 204)
      - Mercenaries, 1973-1979 (Box 204)
      - Private Armies, 1978-1985 (Box 204)
      - Rhodesian Forces, 1975-1979 (Box 204)
      - South African Involvement, 1976-1986 (Box 204)
    - Politics, 1968-1975, (3 folders) (Box 204)
    - Politics, 1976-1980, Jan., (14 folders) (Box 205)
    - Politics, 1980, Feb.-1982, March, (9 folders) (Box 206)
    - Politics (Box 207)
      - 1982, Apr.-1994, (13 folders) (Box 207)
      - ANC, 1969-1974, (2 folders) (Box 207)
      - ANC, 1975-1992, (3 folders) (Box 208)
      - ANC-ZIC, 1975-1977 (Box 208)
      - Centre Party, 1970-1992 (Box 208)
      - Election Documents, 1979-1985 (Box 208)
      - Frolizi, 1971-1974 (Box 208)
      - Gov. Prop. Agenda, 1969-1986, (3 folders) (Box 208)
      - Liberation Movements, 1970-1982, (4 folders) (Box 208)
      - NUF, 1977-1978 (Box 208)
      - Refugees, 1980 (Box 208)
      - Repression, 1970-1979, (3 folders) (Box 208)
      - Repression, 1980-1993 (Box 209)
      - Rhodesia Party, 1970-1980 (Box 209)
      - UANC, 1976-1981, (3 folders) (Box 209)
      - White Parties, 1966-1989, (5 folders) (Box 209)
      - ZANU, 1971-1981, (8 folders) (Box 209)
      - ZANU, 1982-1989 (Box 210)
      - ZANU-ZAPU merger, 1987-1990 (Box 210)
      - ZANU (Sithole), 1974-1988 (Box 210)
      - ZAPU, 1968-1989, (8 folders) (Box 210)
      - ZIPA, 1975-1978, (2 folders) (Box 210)
      - ZUM, 1989-1992 (Box 210)
      - ZUPO, 1977-1979 (Box 210)
    - Reference (Box 210)
      - 1981-1990 (Box 210)
      - General, 1971-1990 (Box 210)
      - Zimbabwe Project News Bulletin, 1981-1984 (Box 210)
    - Religion, 1971-1993, (3 folders) (Box 210)
    - Society (Box 210)
      - Population, 1969-1993 (Box 210)
      - Urban Integration, 1970-1991 (Box 210)
      - Whites, 1980-1994 (Box 210)
    - Sports, 1974-1994 (Box 210)
    - Women, 1977-1994 (Box 210)
- U.S. Economy (Box 210)
  These files were established to provide general background information about the U.S. economy and are not specifically related to Africa. Topics include agriculture, banking, environment, inflation, telecommunications, and trade.
  - 1970-1992, (8 folders) (Box 211)
  - Agriculture (Box 211)
  - Agriculture: Exports (Box 211)
  - Banks (Box 211)
  - Bibliography/Book Reviews (Box 211)
  - Blacks (Box 211)
  - Budget (Box 211)
  - Charity (Box 211)
  - Commodities (Box 211)
  - Corporations (Box 212)
    - through 1989, (3 folders) (Box 212)
    - Corporate Financing (Box 212)
    - Corporate Responsibility (Box 212)
    - S.E.C. (Box 212)
    - Shareholders Campaign, through 1983, (3 folders) (Box 212)
  - Energy (Box 212)
    - Bibliography (Box 212)
    - Non-Oil Sources (Box 212)
    - Oil, through 1990, (7 folders) (Box 212)
    - Policy (Box 213)
    - through 1990, (4 folders) (Box 213)
    - Synthetic Fuels (Box 213)
  - Environment: Pesticides (Box 213)
  - Federal Reserve (Box 213)
  - Finance and Investment (Box 213)
    - Foreign in U.S. (Box 213)
    - U.S. Overseas, through 1973, 1978-1990, (4 folders) (Box 213)
    - Direct Investment Abroad Data (Box 213)
    - Overseas Lending Surveys, 1981-1985 (Box 213)
    - Overseas Lending Surveys, 1986-1988 (Box 214)
  - Fishing (Box 214)
  - Food (Box 214)
  - Foreign Economic Policy (Box 214)
  - Housing (Box 214)
  - Income Distribution (Box 214)
  - Industry (Box 214)
    - Airplanes (Box 214)
    - Automobiles (Box 214)
    - Computers (Box 214)
    - Liquor (Box 214)
    - Steel (Box 214)
    - Textiles (Box 214)
    - Tires (Box 214)
  - Inflation (Box 214)
  - Insurance Companies (Box 214)
  - Minerals (Box 214)
  - Minorities (Box 214)
  - Monetary (Box 214)
  - Nuclear (Box 214)
    - through 1989, (5 folders) (Box 214)
    - Enrichment (Box 214)
    - Exports, through 1982, (4 folders) (Box 214)
    - Plutonium (Box 214)
    - Safety (Box 214)
  - Population (Box 215)
  - Reference Sources (Box 215)
  - Regions (Box 215)
  - Sanctions (Box 215)
  - Southern Development (Box 215)
  - Telecommunications (Box 215)
  - Trade, through 1991, (7 folders) (Box 215)
  - Trade Deficit (Box 215)
  - Transnational Corp. (Box 215)
  - Transportation (Box 215)
  - Workers (Box 215)
  - Workers: Union Busting (Box 215)
- U.S. Education (Box 215)
  - Education, (1 folder) (Box 215)
- U.S. Foreign Policy (Box 215)
  This series focuses on U.S. foreign policy concerns in broad topics such as the CIA, human rights, immigration, Peace Corps., terrorism, and United Nations. These topics may include Africa-related issues; however, most of the files related to U. S. foreign policy toward Africa are located in series, "U.S. Foreign Relations: Africa" and "U. S. Foreign Relations: African Countries."
  - Agribusiness (Box 215)
  - Bibliography (Box 215)
  - CIA (Box 215)
    - Africa, 1975-1987, (3 folders) (Box 215)
    - Asia (Box 215)
    - Assassinations (Box 215)
    - Bibliography (Box 215)
    - Chile (Box 215)
    - Domestic Spying (Box 215)
    - Europe (Box 216)
    - Experiments (Box 216)
    - General, through 1986, (15 folders) (Box 216)
    - General, 1987-1993 (Box 217)
    - Labor (Box 217)
    - Latin America (Box 217)
    - Middle East (Box 217)
    - News Media (Box 217)
    - "Proprietaries" (Box 217)
    - Universities (Box 217)
  - Colonial Possessions, 1977-1978 (Box 217)
  - Congress (Box 217)
    - House, through 1993, (3 folders) (Box 217)
    - Senate, through 1987, (2 folders) (Box 217)
  - Disarmament, through 1988, (6 folders) (Box 217)
  - Economic Policy, through 1979 (Box 217)
  - Economic Policy, 1980-1989, (3 folders) (Box 218)
  - Education (Box 218)
  - Environment (Box 218)
  - Food, through 1983 (Box 218)
  - Foreign Agents (Box 218)
  - Foreign Aid, through 1979, (5 folders) (Box 218)
  - Foreign Aid, 1980-1993, (7 folders) (Box 219)
    - Debt Relief (Box 219)
    - Documents (Box 219)
  - Foreign Diplomats (Box 219)
  - Foreign Names Committee (Box 219)
  - Foreign Students (Box 219)
  - General, through 1978, May (Box 219)
  - General, 1978 June-1993, (11 folders) (Box 220)
  - Helsinki Accord (Box 220)
  - Human Rights, through 1993, (7 folders) (Box 220)
  - IMF (Box 221)
  - Immigration (Box 221)
  - Labor (Box 221)
  - Languages (Box 221)
  - Laws of the Sea, through 1989 (Box 221)
  - Lobbying (Box 221)
  - Media (Box 221)
  - Minerals, through 1983, (5 folders) (Box 221)
  - Narcotics (Box 221)
  - N.S.A (National Security Agency) (Box 221)
  - National Security Council (Box 221)
  - Nuclear (Box 221)
    - Proliferation (Box 221)
    - Protest & Action (Box 221)
  - Peace Corps, through 1985 (Box 221)
  - Peace Corps, 1986-1993 (Box 222)
    - 25th Anniversary (Box 222)
  - Population (Box 222)
  - Public Opinion Polls (Box 222)
  - Refugees (Box 222)
  - Science & Technology (Box 222)
  - State Department, through 1989, (7 folders) (Box 222)
  - Terrorism (Box 222)
  - Trade (Box 223)
    - Export Policy Clips (Box 223)
  - U.N., through 1993, (9 folders) (Box 223)
    - Peacekeeping (Box 223)
    - UNESCO (Box 223)
    - Special Session Disarmament (Box 223)
  - USIA (Box 223)
    - ICA (Box 223)
    - VOA (Box 223)
- U.S. Foreign Relations: Africa (Box 223)
  In this series the beginning files focus on Africa as a continent; thereafter files are arranged alphabetically intermixing individual African countries and African regions. In distinguishing foreign policy from foreign relations -- foreign policy focuses more on establishing positions related to issues while foreign relations deal with the interaction between the countries based on the foreign policy. Within the files there is information about ambassadorial appointments, meetings with high officials, and cultural, educational, and scientific exchanges. Related materials are in the series, "U. S. Politics."
  NOTE: Additional topics in this category regarding Clinton Foreign Policy are listed at the end (Accession 2000-0208).
  - African-Americans, 1981-1996 (Box 224)
  - African Studies (Box 224)
  - Aid, 1970-1997 ( 8 folders) (Box 224)
    - Initiatives (Box 224)
    - USA for Africa--Live Aid, 1985-1995 (Box 224)
  - Arms, 1976-1983 (Box 224)
  - Bibliography, 1974-1991 (Box 224)
  - Congress, 1969-1990, (4 folders) (Box 224)
  - Congress, 1991-1996 (Box 225)
  - Cultural, 1978-1995, (9 folders) (Box 225)
  - Democratic Party, 1966-1988, (2 folders) (Box 225)
  - Economy, 1974-1996, (4 folders) (Box 225)
    - Private Sector, 1981-1994 (Box 225)
  - Films, 1982-1993, (2 folders) (Box 225)
  - General, 1962-1970 (Box 225)
  - General, 1970-1980, (14 folders) (Box 226)
  - General, 1981-1993, (6 folders) (Box 227)
  - Immigration, 1986-1993 (Box 227)
  - Intelligence, 1981-1994 (Box 227)
  - Lobbyists, 1980-1992 (Box 227)
  - Military, 1983-1997 (Box 227)
    - Mercenaries Issue, 1976-1978 (Box 227)
  - Oyotunji, 1973-1977 (Box 227)
  - "Roots", 1977-1980 (Box 227)
  - Sports, 1978-1986 (Box 227)
  - Tourism, 1986-1994 (Box 227)
  - Women, 1988 (Box 227)
  - Visitors, 1975-1992 (Box 227)
  - COUNTRIES & REGIONS (Box 227)
    - Algeria, 1973-1994, (3 folders) (Box 227)
    - Angola, 1975, (2 folders) (Box 227)
    - Angola, through 1992, (12 folders) (Box 228)
      - Aid to UNITA, 1986-1989, (3 folders) (Box 228)
      - Aid to UNITA, 1990-1994, (2 folders) (Box 229)
      - Iran-Contra Connection, 1986-1989 (Box 229)
    - Benin (Box 229)
    - Botswana (Box 229)
    - Burkina Fasso (Upper Volta) (Box 229)
    - Burundi (Box 229)
    - Cameroon (Box 229)
    - Cape Verde (Box 229)
    - Central African (Empire) Republic (Box 229)
    - Chad (Box 229)
    - Congo (Box 229)
    - Diego Garcia (Box 229)
    - Djibouti (Box 229)
    - East Africa (Box 229)
    - Egypt, through 1994, (10 folders) (Box 229)
    - Eritrea (Box 230 Equatorial Guinea)
    - Ethiopia, (7 folders) (Box 230 Equatorial Guinea)
    - Gabon (Box 230 Equatorial Guinea)
    - Gambia (Box 230 Equatorial Guinea)
    - Ghana (Box 230 Equatorial Guinea)
    - Guinea-Bissau (Box 230 Equatorial Guinea)
    - Guinea (Conakry) (Box 230 Equatorial Guinea)
    - Horn of Africa, (4 folders) (Box 230 Equatorial Guinea)
      - Horn of Africa Food and Security Act (Box 230 Equatorial Guinea)
    - Indian Ocean (Box 230 Equatorial Guinea)
    - Ivory Coast (Box 230 Equatorial Guinea)
    - Kenya, (2 folders) (Box 230 Equatorial Guinea)
    - Lesotho (Box 230 Equatorial Guinea)
    - Liberia, through 1994, (6 folders) (Box 231)
    - Libya, through 1981, Sept., (5 folders) (Box 231)
    - Libya (Box 232)
      - 1981, Oct.-1992, (10 folders) (Box 232)
      - Chemical Weapons Plant, 1987-1989, (2 folders) (Box 232)
    - Malagasy (Madagascar) (Box 232)
    - Malawi (Box 232)
    - Mali (Box 232)
    - Mauritania (Box 232)
    - Mauritius (Box 232)
    - Morocco, through 1977 (Box 232)
    - Morocco, 1978-1988, (6 folders) (Box 233)
    - Mozambique (Box 233)
      - 1975-1989, (4 folders) (Box 233)
      - Renamo (Box 233)
    - Namibia, 1967-1994 (folders) (Box 233)
    - Niger (Box 234)
    - Nigeria, 1973-1983, (4 folders) (Box 234)
    - North Africa, 1980-1991 (Box 234)
    - Portugal & Portuguese Colonialism (Box 234)
      - 1961-1974, (4 folders) (Box 234)
      - Since April 1974 Coup (Box 234)
      - Economy, through 1974 (Box 234)
      - Military (Box 234)
      - Military: Africa, 1975 DOD Report (Box 234)
    - Rwanda (Box 234)
    - Sahel (Box 234)
    - Sao Tome & Principe (Box 234)
    - Senegal (Box 234)
    - Seychelles (Box 234)
    - Sierra Leone (Box 234)
    - Somalia, 1974-1992, Sept., (5 folders) (Box 234)
    - Somalia (Box 235)
      - 1993-1994, (4 folders) (Box 235)
      - Operation Restore Hope, 1992, Dec.-1995, June, (3 folders) (Box 235)
      - Opinion and Comment on Operation Restore Hope, 1992-1993, (2 folders) (Box 235)
      - International Assistance for Restore Hope (Box 235)
    - South Africa, 1961-1978, June, (11 folders) (Box 236)
    - South Africa, 1978, July-1985, July, (10 folders) (Box 237)
    - South Africa (Box 238)
      - 1985, Aug.-1994, (7 folders) (Box 238)
      - American Bar Association (Box 238)
      - A.N.C., through 1990, (2 folders) (Box 238)
        - Mandela Visit, 1990, June 17-22; 1990, June 23-July 1, (2 folders) (Box 238)
          - Visit Preparations (Box 238)
          - Editorial Opinion on Mandela (Box 238)
          - Post Visit (Box 238)
      - Bantustans, 1976-1990, (2 folders) (Box 239)
      - Bibliography (Box 239)
        - The Cordoned Heart (Box 239)
      - Churches/Clergy (Box 239)
      - Congress, 1966-1988 (Box 239)
      - Congress, 1989 -1993 (Box 240)
      - Culture (Box 240)
        - 1972-1988, (7 folders) (Box 240)
        - Films (Box 240)
        - Sun City (Box 240)
      - Economy, through 1978, June, (7 folders) (Box 240)
      - Economy (Box 241)
        - 1978, July-1992, (6 folders) (Box 241)
        - Aid, 1993 (Box 241)
        - Coal, through 1981, (3 folders) (Box 241)
        - Divestment, 1978-1992, (11 folders) (Box 241)
        - Divestment (Box 242)
          - Bank Loans, through 1993, (5 folders) (Box 242)
          - Companies, through 1990 (Box 242)
          - Lists of Companies (Box 242)
      - Divestment (Box 242)
        - High Tech Sales to S.A. (Box 242)
        - Local Governments, through 1991 (Box 242)
        - Religion, through 1979 (Box 242)
        - Religion, 1980-1992, (2 folders) (Box 243)
      - Economy (Box 243)
        - Sanctions Busting (Box 243)
        - Sanctions Busting: ARMS (Box 243)
        - Eximport Bank, through 1978 (Box 243)
        - Investment, (2 folders) (Box 243)
        - Gold Ownership (Box 243)
        - Krugerrand, 1976-1985, (5 folders) (Box 243)
        - Minerals (Box 243)
        - Nuclear, through 1981 (Box 243)
        - Nuclear, 1982-1993 (Box 244)
        - Sealskins (Box 244)
        - South African Airways (Box 244)
        - Sugar Quota (Box 244)
        - Sullivan Principles (Box 244)
        - Tourism, 1977- (Box 244)
          - Trade (Box 244)
          - 1981-1987 (Box 244)
          - Arms Embargo (Box 244)
          - Arms Embargo Guidelines (Box 244)
          - Computers (Box 244)
          - Export Regulations (Box 244)
          - 1981/1982 Debate (Box 244)
          - Shock Batons (Box 244)
        - Trade Unions (Box 244)
        - Editorial Opinions (Box 244)
        - Editorial Opinions, 1986-1992 (Box 245)
      - Health (Box 245)
      - Inkatha (Box 245)
      - Intelligence (Box 245)
      - Lobbyists (Box 245)
      - Military (Box 245)
        - 1970-1992, (7 folders) (Box 245)
        - Draft Resistance (Box 245)
        - Terrorism Hearings, 1982, Pt. 1 & 2, (2 folders) (Box 245)
      - Police (Box 245)
      - Polls (Box 245)
      - Project for South Africa (Box 245)
      - Protest and Action, through 1978 (Box 245)
      - Protest and Action (Box 246)
        - 1979-1990, (6 folders) (Box 246)
        - Campuses, through 1986, (7 folders) (Box 246)
        - Campuses, 1987-1991 (Box 247)
      - Republican Party (Box 247)
      - Sport, through 1993, (7 folders) (Box 247)
      - U.S. Residents in South Africa, (2 folders) (Box 247)
      - Visits and Exchanges (Box 247)
        - USSALEP (Box 247)
        - Tutu, Boesak (Box 247)
    - Southern Africa (Box 248)
      - 1961-1979, (16 folders) (Box 248)
    - Southern Africa (Box 249)
      - 1980-1981, 1983, 1987-1990, (5 folders) (Box 249)
      - Black Americans (Box 249)
      - Congress, through 1993, (3 folders) (Box 249)
      - Drought, 1992 (Box 249)
      - Economy, through 1990, (3 folders) (Box 249)
      - Editorial Opinion (Box 249)
      - Misson Nisdom, Etc. (Box 249)
      - NSSM 39 Study (Document) (Box 249)
      - Protest & Action, through 1986, (5 folders) (Box 249)
      - Protest & Action, 1987- (Box 250)
      - Reference (Box 250)
      - Right Wing Groups (Box 250)
      - South African Opinion, through 1978, (2 folders) (Box 250)
    - Sudan, through 1994, (5 folders) (Box 250)
    - Swaziland (Box 250)
    - Tanzania, through 1992, (3 folders) (Box 250)
    - Togo (Box 250)
    - Tunisia (Box 250)
    - Uganda, through 1993, (4 folders) (Box 250)
    - Upper Volta (Box 250)
    - Western Sahara (Box 250)
      - through 1992, (2 folders) (Box 250)
      - Support Activities (Box 250)
      - State Department Conference (Box 250)
    - Zaire (Box 251)
      - 1975-1994, (9 folders) (Box 251)
      - Economy (Box 251)
    - Zambia, 1970-1993, (4 folders) (Box 251)
    - Zimbabwe/Rhodesia (Box 252)
      - 1961-1977, (5 folders) (Box 252)
      - Byrd Amendment (Box 252)
        - 1971-1977, (6 folders) (Box 252)
        - Protest at Docks (Box 252)
        - List of Congresses, 1973 (Box 252)
    - Zimbabwe/Rhodesia (Box 253)
      - 1978, Jan.-1994, (15 folders) (Box 253)
- U.S. Foreign Relations: Non-African Countries (Box 253)
  These files are arranged alphabetically by country and primarily focus on situations where cooperation or non-cooperation over policy in Africa was an issue.
  - Afghanistan (Box 254)
  - Asia (Box 254)
  - Australia (Box 254)
  - Brazil (Box 254)
  - Canada (Box 254)
  - Caribbean (Box 254)
  - Central America (Box 254)
  - Chile (Box 254)
  - China (PRC), 1977-1983, (3 folders) (Box 254)
  - Cuba (Box 254)
  - El Salvador, 1981-1982, (5 folders) (Box 254)
  - Europe (Box 254)
  - France (Box 254)
  - Grenada (Box 254)
  - Haiti (Box 254)
  - India (Box 254)
  - Indian Ocean (Box 254)
  - Indonesia (Box 254)
  - Iran, 1974-1978, (2 folders) (Box 254)
  - Iran (Box 255)
    - 1979-1989, (3 folders) (Box 255)
    - Iran-Contra (Box 255)
  - Israel (Box 255)
  - Jamaica (Box 255)
  - Japan (Box 255)
  - Korea (Box 255)
  - Latin America, through 1989, (4 folders) (Box 255)
  - Lebanon (Box 255)
  - Mexico (Box 255)
  - Middle East, through 1993, (8 folders) (Box 255)
  - Nicaragua (Box 256)
  - Oman (Box 256)
  - Pacific Islands (Box 256)
  - Pakistan (Box 256)
  - Palestine/P.L.O. (Box 256)
  - Panama (Box 256)
  - Philippines (Box 256)
  - Poland (Box 256)
  - Portugal (Box 256)
    - 1974- (Box 256)
    - Economy (Box 256)
  - Saudi Arabia (Box 256)
  - Spain (Box 256)
  - Taiwan (Box 256)
  - Third World (Box 256)
  - Trilateral Countries (Box 256)
  - Turkey (Box 256)
  - United Kingdom (Box 256)
  - U.S.S.R. (Box 256)
    - 1974-1993, (8 folders) (Box 256)
    - Afghan Crisis (Box 256)
    - Grain Embargo (Box 256)
  - Vietnam (Box 256)
  - West Germany (Box 256)
  - Yemen (Box 256)
  - Yugoslavia (Box 256)
- U.S. - Africa Groups (Box 256)
  These are U. S. groups that have some connection with Africa, such as Americans Concerned About South Africa, Gulf Boycott Coalition, and the Washington Office on Africa. These groups formed around political, humanitarian, educational or cultural concerns and range from small local entities to large national groups and branches of international organizations. Some of these organizations no longer exist either because they did not survive over time or because they were formed to respond to a specific event or issue that has passed. There are related files in series, "U.S. Groups," "North Carolina," and "World."
  - "A" (Box 257)
    - AFRAM Associates (Box 257)
    - Africa Faith and Justice Network (Box 257)
    - Africa Fund (see American Committee on Africa) (Box 257)
    - Africa Information Service (Box 257)
    - Africa Media & News Agency (Box 257)
    - Africa Peace Committee (Box 257)
    - Africa Research Group (Box 257)
      - Publications (Box 257)
    - Africa University (see United Methodist Church--Africa Programs) (Box 257)
    - African Agenda, 1972-1977, (2 folders) (Box 257)
    - African-American Chamber of Commerce (Box 257)
    - African-American Institute, thru 1977 (Box 257)
      - Women in African Development (Box 257)
      - Reference (Box 257)
    - African-American Labor Center (Box 257)
    - African-American Scholars Council (Box 258)
    - African Bibliographic Center (Box 258)
    - African Development and Human Relations Movement (Box 258)
    - African Development Foundation (Box 258)
    - African Development Information Association (Box 258)
    - African Institute of Cultural Relations (Box 258)
    - African Liberation Solidarity Committee (Box 258)
    - African Liberation Support Committee (Box 258)
      - African Liberation Day (Box 258)
    - ALA - African Literature Association (Box 258)
    - The African Medical and Research Foundation (AMREF) (Box 258)
    - APSP (Box 258)
    - African Progressive Study Group (Box 258)
    - African Studies Association (Box 258)
    - Africa Studies Center (Boston University) (Box 258)
    - African Youth Movement for Liberation and Unity (Box 258)
    - Africare, thru 1993, (2 folders) (Box 258)
    - AfricaTrek (Box 258)
    - Afrika Must Unite (Box 258)
    - Afro-Americans Against the Drought (Box 258)
    - Afro-Americans Against the Famine (Box 258)
    - All-African News Service (Box 258)
    - All African People's Revolutionary Party (Box 258)
    - Amandla Production Group (Box 259)
    - American African Affairs Association (Box 259)
    - American African Relief Foundation (Box 259)
    - American Committee on Africa, thru 1990, (7 folders) (Box 259)
    - American Committee on Africa Publications (Box 259)
    - American Coordinating Committee in Sport and Society (ACCESS) (Box 259)
    - Americans Concerned About South Africa (ACSA) (Box 259)
    - Americans Against Apartheid (Box 259)
    - American Southern Africa Council (Box 259)
    - Americans for Freedom in Southern Africa (Box 259)
    - Angola Peace Fund (Box 259)
    - Angola Support Conference (Box 259)
    - Anti-Apartheid Committee for Selective Purchasing (Box 259)
    - Anti-Apartheid Movement (AAM) (Box 259)
    - Artists and Athletes Against Apartheid (Box 259)
    - Association for Constitutional Democracy in Liberia (Box 259)
    - Association of African Historians (Box 259)
    - Association of Americans to Save Africa (Box 259)
    - Austin Committee to Oppose Racism and Apartheid (Box 259)
  - "B" (Box 259)
    - BA-NAG (Box 259)
    - Bishop Tutu's Refugee Fund (Box 259)
    - Bishop Tutu Scholarship Fund (Box 259)
    - Blojlu's Alliance (Liberia) (Box 259)
    - BA-SHIRU (University of Wisconsin) (Box 259)
    - Boston Coalition for the Liberation of South Africa (Box 259)
  - "C" (Box 259)
    - Cabral Memorial Committee (Box 259)
    - Cape Verdian-American Federation (Box 259)
    - Center for Economic Research on Africa (Box 259)
    - Center for Intergroup Studies (Box 259)
    - Chicago Coalition for Liberation of Angola, Mozambique, Guinea (Box 259)
    - Chicago Committee for African Liberation (Box 259)
    - Chicago Coalition on Southern Africa (Box 259)
    - Churches (Ecumenical Projects) (Box 260)
    - Church Project on U.S. Investment in Southern Africa (Box 260)
    - Coalition for a Free Africa (Box 260)
    - Coalition for Human Rights in South Africa (Box 260)
    - Coalition for the Liberation of Southern Africa (CLSA) (Box 260)
    - Coalition for Peace in the Horn of Africa (Box 260)
    - Coalition on Southern Africa, 1987 (Box 260)
    - Coalition to Stop Rhodesian Imports (Box 260)
    - Committee for a Free Mozambique (Box 260)
    - Committee for an Afro-American Liberation Center (Box 260)
    - Committee on African Development Strategies (Box 260)
    - Committee to Support the Independence of Guinea-Bissau (Box 260)
    - Concerned African Students (North Carolina) (Box 260)
    - Concerned Citizens Committee on Africa (Box 260)
    - Contrast (Box 260)
    - Corporate Campaign Africa (Box 260)